{
    "name": "Antonyms",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grasso",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519668424.7673283,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"magro\"",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "magro",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519668457.706511,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"grasso\"",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sincero",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519668444.3671708,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"bugiardo\"",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pesante",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519668441.8311994,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"leggero\"",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "puzzolente",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519668454.482553,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"profumato\"",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "allegro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668364.0481539,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"triste\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bugiardo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668427.5748694,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"sincero\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "leggero",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668422.339545,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"pesante\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arrabbiato",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519668528.4187276,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"tranquillo\"",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intelligente",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519668518.329485,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"sciocco\"",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bello",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668491.694067,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"brutto\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pulito",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668509.7778847,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"sporco\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668505.8779776,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"basso\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pieno",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668515.594542,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"vuoto\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vuoto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668494.294361,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"pieno\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giovane",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668513.1548083,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"vecchio\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "caldo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668536.4494824,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"freddo\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "triste",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668540.9368834,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"allegro\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "basso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668542.9370756,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"alto\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sporco",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668565.9887338,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"pulito\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vecchio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668545.597188,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"giovane\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668548.0297174,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"piccolo\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tranquillo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668532.5216718,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"arrabbiato\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sciocco",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668571.916765,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"intelligente\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piccolo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519668597.5766926,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"grande\"",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "brutto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668574.6252835,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"bello\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "freddo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668579.3443553,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"caldo\"",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "profumato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519668592.5048633,
            "question": "What is the antonym of \"puzzolente\"",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}